Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Jesse Ely Wills Papers
1912 ’ 1920
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0001
2.52 linear feet
Biography/Scope and Content Note
Jesse Ely Wills, 1899-1977, a Nashville native, was a member of the group of poets who met in Nashville in the early 1920's to write and publish the influential literary magazine The Fugitive. He was an officer and executive of the National Life and Accident Insurance Company during his business career and was active in Vanderbilt University affairs as a member of the Board of Trust and chairman of the Board of the Joint University Libraries.
This collection contains literary correspondence, poems, and manuscripts of poet and businessman Jesse Ely Wills.
- Correspondence - Outgoing. 1952-77. Arranged chronologically. 484 letters, the bulk of which consists of typed carbons. Folders 1-6. (Folder 1.)
- Correspondence - Incoming. 1951-76. 492 letters, most typed, many holograph. Six postcards, three Christinas cards. Two telegrams. Arranged alphabetically according to sender. Folders 7-14. (Folder 1.)
- Enclosures - Miscellaneous essays and reviews by Jesse E. Wills, newspaper clippings, photographs of Robert Penn Warren bust, essays by others, reprint essays of others, items showing his relationship with Allen Tate, miscellaneous papers. Folders 15-21. (Folder 1.)
- Old Oak and Coffee House Papers 1930-1969, including drafts and later supplements to the papers. Folder 1. (Folder 2.)
- Juvenilia, c. 1915-20. Folder 2. (Folder 2.)
- Fugitive verse, 1922-25. Folders 3-4. (Folder 2.)
- Economic Discussion Group, 1931-33. Folder 5. (Folder 2.)
- Early and Late - Rough drafts, intermediate and final drafts, typescript (printer's 'copy), page proofs, business correspondence, congratulatory correspondence, reviews. Folders 1-6. (Folder 3)
- Notes, remarks on poetry readings. Folder 7. (Folder 3)
- Introduction of Jesse E. Wills on occasion of a poetry reading, 12 November 1971, by Frances Neel Cheney. Folder 8. (Folder 3)
- Tapes of poetry reading by Jesse E. Wills. 12 November 1971, 14 November 1973. Script of WPLN broadcast with Lin Folk, 8 April 1977. Folder 9. (Folder 3)
- Meditations on the American Indian - Drafts, typescript (printer's copy), page proofs, published copy in paper cover. Folders 10-12. (Folder 3)
- Conversation Piece - Notes and early drafts, intermediate and final drafts, page proofs, analytical letter from Donald Davidson. Folders 1-5. (Folder 4)
- Nashville and Other Poems - Notes and early drafts, intermediate and final drafts, typescript (printer's copy), page proofs. Folders 6-11. (Folder 4)
- Selected Poems - Early drafts, page proofs, correspondence» reviews. Folders 1-3. (Folder 5)
- á. Diversity of Interests - Draft copies, typescript, printer's copy, correspondence, essays not included in the publication, published copy in paper covers. Folders 4-9. (Folder 5)
- Occasional verse. Folder 10. (Folder 5)
- "First Lady" - Several drafts of a contemplated poem on Mrs. John F. Kennedy. Not completed. Folder 11. (Folder 5)
- Vanderbilt affiliations - Correspondence and reports concerning committee work. List of Committees follows: Academic Programs Committee. Folders 1-3. Ad hoc Committee on Composition of Undergraduate Student Body. .Folder 4. Committee for Fort Flowers Wing Dedication. Folder 5. Committee on Naming Buildings. Folder 6. Committee on Strengthening Athletics. Folder 7. Educational Programs Committee. Folder 8. Ethiopian Microfilming Project. Folder 9. Fraternity Study Committee. Folder 10. Graduate School of Management. Folder 11. JUL Building Fund. Folder 12. JUL Fugitive Room. Folder 13. Lawson Case. Folder 14. Long-Range Financial Planning Committee. Folder 15. (Folder 6)
- List of Committees continued: Ponzine, Raymond E. and Huber, Donald C. - Poetry Reading at Vanderbilt. Folder 16. Resolutions on the death of Vanderbilt Associates. Folder 17. Telecast of Basketball Games. Folder 18. W.R. Wills Center for Psychiatric Treatment and Research. Folder 19. (Folder 6)
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Correspondence is listed chronologically. Folder indicated by abbreviation F.
- 26 August to Merrill Moore; 26 August to Coley Harwell; F. 1-1., 1952 (Box 1)
- 8 November to George Mayfield; F. 1-1., 1954
- 15 June to "Red" (Robert Fenn Warren); F. 1-1. 31 July to William F. Orr; F. 6-14. 5 September to William 0. Batts; F. 1-1., 1956
- 30 April to Allen Tate; 9 June to Allen Tate; 9 June to. "Bill" (William Yandell Elliott); F. 1-1. 17 December to "Lib" (Mrs. R.D. Crabtree); F. 3-4., 1958
- 7 January to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 3-4. 7 April to Ann Leslie Moore; 10 April to Allen Tate; 29 April to Caroline Gordon; 18 May to Ann Leslie Moore; F. 1-1., 1959
- 1960, 10 March to Eldon Stevenson, Jr., (unsigned); F. 6-14. 22 April to Sally (Mrs. Lewis Barr Flinn, Jr.); F. 1-1. 2 June to Harvey Branscomb; F. 6-14. 29 December to Howard Hall; F. 6-14.
- 22 February to Guy Owen; 26 December to Guy Owen; F. 1-1., 1961
- 3 January to Guy Owen; 9 April to Allen Tate; 15 May to Allen Tate; 23 May to James M. Waller; 10 September to Mrs. Brainard Cheney; F. 1-1., 1962
- 7 November to Andrew Lytle; F. 1-1., 1963
- 9 January to Rob Roy Furdy; F. 6-18. 26 March to Lawrence S. Thompson; 24 December to Matt Wigginton; F. 1-1., 1964
- 24 May to Horace Hill; 11 June to Horace Hill; 14 June to Fort Flowers; 14 June to Alexander Heard; 14 June to Alexander Heard; 1 July to Harold Vanderbilt; F. 6-12. 3 August to Reber Boult; 12 October to Rob Roy Purdy; 18 October to Frances Neel Cheney (Mrs. Brainard); F. 1-1., 1965
- 4 January to Jud Collins; 4 January to John H. Dewitt, Jr.; F. 6-18. 4 February to David Howell Jones; 9 February to Allen Tate; 10 February to Donald Davidson; 23 February to Allen Tate; 25 February to J. Lasley Dameron; F. 1-2. 18 March to David Kaser; 18 March to Alec Stevenson; F. 6-12., 1966
- 29 April to Peter J. Tharp; 22 August to Allen Tate; 4 October to Edith H. Wolfe; 24 October to Alec Stevenson; 25 October to Donald Davidson; 25 October to John Crowe Ransom; 25 October to Allen Tate; 25 October to Robert Penn Warren; 30 October to Donald Davidson; 2 November to Margaret Williams; 14 November to Allen Tate; 15 November to Robert Penn Warren; 6 December to Henry E. Niles; F. 1-2., 1966
- 5 April to Ridley Wills; 18 April to Rob Roy Purdy; 18 April to Rob Roy Purdy; 24 April to Steve (Alec B. Stevenson); 9 May to Robert Penn Warren, Alec B. Stevenson; 18 May to Donald Davidson; 22 May to Edwin F. Hunt; 25 May to Alec B. Stevenson» Rob Roy Purdy; 25 July to Robert Penn Warren; 4 August to Allen Tate; 11 October to Louis Farrell» Jr.; 12 October to James K. Flack; 26 October to Margaret Williams; F. 1-2. 1 November to James A. Simpson, William Waller, Sr.; F. 6-17. 15 November to James K. Flack; F. 1-2. 16 November to Robert L. Garner; F. 6-13. 18 December to Floy Beaty; F. 1-2., 1967
- 12 January to Elizabeth and John K. Maddin; 24 January to James K. Flack» Andrew Lytle; 25 January to Allen Tate; 13 February to Allen Tate; 5 March to Greg Tucker; 18 March to Allen Tate; 8 April to Robert Penn Warren; 22 April to Robert Penn Warren, Matthew B. Wills; 24 April to William C. Pratt; 25 April to Allen Tate, Andrew Lytle; 7 May to James M. Waller; 20 May to William C. Pratt, Robert Penn Warren; 27 May to Allen Tate; F. 1-3. 28 May to David Käser; F. 6-13. 10 June to Ann Leslie Moore; 12 June to Edwin S. Gardner; 2 July to Allen Tate; 8 July to Mrs. Merrill Moore; F. 1-3. 8 July to Roy B. Basler; F. 6-13. 11 July to Ann Leslie Moore; 15 July to Allen Tate; 18 July to Robert Penn Warren; 1 August to Mr. and Mrs. Allen Tate, Andrew Lytle; 5 August to Allen Tate; 6 August to Randolph Harrison; 3 September to Ernest Choate; 11 September to May (Mrs. David F, Hall); 16 September to Allen Tate, Pete (Robert L. Naylor); 18 September to Allen Tate; 23 September to Allen Tate; F. 1-3. 30 September to Alec B. Stevenson; F. 6-17. 9 October to Frank Grisham; F. 6-13. 20 November to Thomas D. Young; F. 1-3. 5 December to Alexander Heard; F. 6-5. 5 December to John aSloan; F. 6-7. 17 December to Alec B. Stevenson, George Cate, Jr.» Mrs. Albert Werthan, John Bransford; F. 6-5. 19 December to Allen Tate; 30 December to Edwin S. Gardner; F. 1-3., 1968
- 2 January to Alexander Heard, Matt S. Wigginton, George Cate, Jr., Mrs. Albert Werthan, John Bransford, Alec B, Stevenson; F, 6-5. 9 January to Allen Tate, Alec B. Stevenson; 13 January to T. Daniel Young; 20 January to Allen Tate; 3 February to Allen Tate; 4 February to Allen Tate, Thomas D. Young; 5 February to Allen Tate; F. 1-3. 5 February to Alec B. Stevenson; F. 6-13. 6 February to William S. Vaughn; F. 6-1. 6 February to 1969; Frank Grisham; F. 6-5. 10 February to Edwin S. Gardner; F. 6-13. 10 February to Mrs. Merrill Moore; 11 February to Thomas Daniel Young, Allen Tate; 27 February to Themas Daniel Young; 4 March to Thomas Daniel Young, Mrs. Merrill Moore; 12 March to Allen Tate; 17 March to Frank P. Grisham; 18 March to Allen Tate; 19 March to Donald Davidson, Rob Roy Purdy; 31 March to Allen Tate, William Yandell Elliott, Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-3. 31 March to Madison S. Wigginton, Frank P. Grisham; F. 6-13. 10 April to James A. Simpson, William H. Vanderbilt; F. 6-1. 10 April to Alec B. Stevenson; 14 April to Thomas F. Heffernan; F. 1-3. 15 April to William Waller; F. 6-1. 21 April to Mrs. Betsy Wilson; 20 April to Geddes Douglas, Sr.; 29 April to. Allen Tate; 29 April to Alec B. Stevenson; 19 May to William Yandell Elliott,;Allen Tate, Robert Penn Warren; 20 May to Carolyn and William A. Mc Donnell; F. 1-3. 26 May to Matt S. Wigginton; 27 May to Robert A. McGaw; F. 6-13. 27 May to Robert Penn Warren; 28 May to Edwin S. Gardner, William Yandell Elliott; 29 May to Orrin W. Jones; F. 1-3. 2 June to Charles S. Ragland; F. 6-1. 3 June to Woodrow W. Wasson; F. 6-13. 12 June to Charles S. Ragland, James A. Simpson, Nicholas Hobbs; 16 June to Alexander Heard; F. 6-1. 16 June to Allen Tate; 17 June to William Yandell Elliott; F. 1-3. 18 June to Robert Penn Warren; F, 6-13. 18 June to Charles S. Ragland; F. 6-1. 30 June to Allen Tate, William Yandell Elliott; F. 1-3. 2 July to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 6-1. 7 July to Andrew Lytle; F. 1-3. 8 July to Nancy Manning; F. 6-1. 13 August to William Yandell Elliott; F. 1-3. 28 August to Frank Baker; F. 6-13. 8 September to Allen Tate; F. 1-3. 10 September to Members of the Trustee Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University; F. 6-1» 14 September to Robert A. McGaw, Mr. and Mrs. M.S. Wigginton; 15 September to Elizabeth Wills; F. 1-3. 16 September to Rob Roy PurdjF; F. 6-13. 16 September to Thomas Daniel Young; 17 September to Ann Leslie Moore, Robert Penn Warren; 24 September to Allen Tate; 25 September to Thomas Daniel Young; 29 September to Thomas Daniel Young; F. 1-3. 30 September to Alexander Heard; F. 6-1. 20 October to William H. Vanderbilt; F. 6-1. 21 October to Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-3. 28 October to Andrew Benedict, James G. Stahlman; F. 6-17. 29 October to Members of the Trust Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University; 29 October to Nancy Jane Manning; F. 6-1. 13 December to Mrs. Mapheus Smith; F. 6-13., 1969
- 13 January to Alexander Heard, William S. Vaughn; F. 6-1. 15 January to Robert McGaw; F. 6-6. 15 January to Robert McGaw, Mrs. Mapheus Smith; 19 January to GoIdle D. Hirsch; F. 6-13. 27 January to William S. Vaughn; F. 6-1. 29 January to Forrest Read; F. 1-4. 4 February to Charlie Ragland; F. 6-1. 5 February to Andrew Lytle,Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-4. 5 February to Nicholas Hobbs; 9 February to William Waller; F. 6-1., 1970
- 9 February to Eldon Stevenson; F. 6-6. 16 February to Mrs. Albert Werthan; F. 6-1. 16 February to Mrs. Albert Werthan and Norfleet H. Rand; 19 February to Alexander Heard; F. 6-6. 19 February to William H. Vanderbilt, Charles Ragland; F. 6-1. 2 March to Allen Tate; F. 1-4. 16 March to Norfleet H. Rand; F. 6-6. 17 March to Charles S. Ragland; F. 6-1. 23 March to Allen Tate; F. 1-4. 25 March to Alexander Heard; 26 March to Alexander Heard; F. 6-6. 26 March to Members of the Trust Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University; F. 6-1. 22 April to Members of the Trustee Committee on Academic Programs òf Vanderbilt University; F. 6-8. 27 April to Matt Wigginton; F. 1-4. 28 April to Robert McGaw; F. 6-6. 25 May to Mrs. Merrill Moore; 9 June to Mrs. Merrill Moore; 10 June to Allen Tate, William W. Force; F. 1-4. 6 July to William S. VaVghn; F. 6-1. 8 July to William Yandell Elliott; F. 1-4. 9 July. to Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt; 22 July to Merrimon Cuninggim; F. 6-1. 17 August to Maxey Jarman; 20 August to Margaret Williams; F. 1-4. 14 September to William S. Vaughn; F. 6-17. 17 September to Nicholas Hobbs, William Waller, Merrimon Cuninggim; F. 6-1. 21 October to William Waller; F. 6-17. 26 October to William Waller; F. 6-1. 11 November to Alexander Heard; F. 6-13. 12 November to Vernon Sharp; F. 1-4. 18 November to Robert L. Garner; F. 6-8. 30 November to Allen Tate, John Crowe Ransom; 14 December to Jean and Alexander Heard; 23 December to Thomas D. Young; F. 1-4., 1970
- 16 January to Randolph Batson; 18 January to Robert A. McGaw; 20 January to Matthew B. Wills; 20 January to Robert Sturdivant, Aubrey Harwell; 21 January to Louise Davis; 25 January to Thomas Daniel Young, Allen Tate; 1 February to Mrs. Donald Davidson; 2 February to Jane S. Whitman; 2 March to Walter R. Courtenay; 9 March to Edgar H. Duncan; 15 March to Victor S. Johnson; 16 March to Archie Henry; F. 1-4. 17 March to Frank P. Grisham; F. 6-13. 17 March to Nicholas Hobbs; 24 March to Nicholas Hobbs, Members of the Educational Programs Committee; F. 6-8. 18 March to Thomas D. Young; F. 1-4. 7 April to Allen Tate; 27 April to Chase A. Horton; F. 1-4. 3 May to David E. Wood; F. 6-4. 5 May to Ralph R. Kirkendall; F. 1-4. 6 May to Donald L. Thistlethwaite; 18 May to Donald L. Thistlethwaite; F. 6-4. 19 May to John M. Aden; 7 June to Robert Pénn Warren; 21 June to Mrs. Winston Caldwell; 22 June to Frances Neel Cheney; 30 June to Allen Tate; 15 July to Alexander Heard; 17 July to Thomas Daniel Young; 2 August to Allen Tate; 3 August to Frank P. Grisham; F. 1-4. 9 August to William S. Vaughn; F. 6-1. 29 September to T. H. Hlrschfield; F. 1-4. 30 September to William S. Vaughn; 11 October to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 6-1. 11 October to Mrs. Mapheus Smith; F. 1-4. 13 October to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 6-1. 14 October to Frank Grisham; 1 November to Thomas Daniel Young; 15 November to William Waller; F. 1-4. 15 November to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 6-7. 15 November to Barry L. Master; F. 6-4. 15 November to William S. Vaughn; F. 6-1. 16 November to Robert A. McGaw; 24 November to Frank P. Grisham; 29 November to Fannie (Mrs. Brainard) Cheney; 30 November to, 1971
- Thomas Daniel Young; 9 December to Allen Tate; 20 December to Frank P. Grisham; 21 December to Allen Tate; 31 December to Frank P. Grisham; n.d. December to Frederick J. Dockstader; F. 1-4., 1971
- 24 January to Thomas Daniel Young; 25 January to Andrew Lytle; 3 February to Herschel Gower; 16 February to Mrs. Brainard Cheney, Frank P. Grisham; 21 February to Rob Roy Purdy; 28 February to David Spencer Taber; 14 March to William F. Orr; 20 March to Rob Roy Purdy, Harris D. Riley, Jr.; 23 March to Robert E. Weaver; F. 1-5. 4 April to Nicholas Hobbs; F. 6-8. 4 April to Nicholas Hobbs; 6 April to Nicholas Hobbs; 26 April to Nicholas Hobbs; 8 May to Nicholas Hobbs; F. 6-4. 1 May to Allen Tate; 8 May to Allen Tate, Mrs. Hugh Bullock; 16 May to Thomas Daniel Young; F. 1-5. 12 June to Mrs. Richmond C. Beatty; F. 6-13. 15 June to Mrs. Richmond C.' Beatty; F. 6-13. 21 June to Allen Tate, Thomas Daniel Young; 29 June to Frank K. Houston; 8 August to Thomas Daniel Young; 6 September to Thomas Daniel Young; 14 September to Robert A. McGaw; 20 September to H.L. Swint; 9 October to Robert Penn Warren; 10 October to Thomas Daniel Young; 30 October to Frank P. Grisham, Robert Penn Warren; 21 November to Robert Penn Warren; 14 December to Rob Roy Purdy; 18 December to Robert A. McGaw; F. 1-5. n.d. to Members of the Committee on Academic Programs; F. 6-1., 1972
- 5 March to Allen Tate; 22 March to Andrew Lytle; 11 June to Robert A. McGaw; 7 August to Allen Tate; F. 1-5. 9 August to Frank P. Grisham; F. 6-13. 28 August to Andrew Lytle; F. 1-5. 18 September to Earvie Branscomb; 19 September to E. Bronson Ingram; 25 September to E. Bronson Ingram; F. 6-17. 26 September to Allen Tate; 1 October to Rupert E. Palmer, Jr.; 29 October to Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-5. 21 November to Walter Harrelson; F. 6-9. 3 December to William C. Pratt; 6 December to Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-5., 1973
- 2 January to Walter Harrelson; F. 6-9. 2 January to Allen Tate; 3 January to Daniel T; " • ~- Young; 8 January to Allen Tate; 14 January to Mrs. Eric Bell, Jr.; 15 January to Mr. and Mrs. W.A. Baker; 21 January to Frank P. Grisham, Rupert Palmer; 23 January to Allen Tate; 24 January to Allen Tate; F. 1-5. 29 January to Allen Tate; F. 5-3. 20 February to Allen Tate 4 March to William C. Pratt, Dan Young; 6 March to Allen Tate, Marice Wolfe; 25 March to John W. Poindexter; 1 April to Andrew Lytle; 3 April to Allen Tate; 6 April to Alexander Heard; 10 July to Daniel T. Young; 11 July to Robert A. McGaw; 22 July to Daniel T. Young; 24 July to Frank P. Grisham, Mrs. Alexander Heard; 29 July to Thomas Daniel Young; 31 July to Allen Tate; 1 August to Allen Tate; 14 August to Allen Zibart; 15 August to Allen Tate; 4 September to Allen Tate; 9 September to Allen Tate; 18 September to Edwin Stirling, Allen Tate; 1974: 25 September to Allen Tate; 7 October to Dr. and Mrs« T.E. Brittingham; 14 October to Scott Colley; 31 October to Edwin Sterling; 6 November to Frank Grisham; 18 November to Frank Grisham, Allen Tate; 4 December to Allen Tate; 9 December to M.S. Wigginton, Andres B. Benedict, Jr.» John Bransford; 16 December to Emily Bennett; F. 1-5. 17 December to Allen Tate; F. 5-3. 23 December to John E. Sloan, Jr.; F. 1-5., 1974
- 6 January to lob Roy Purdy; 15 January to Allen Tate; 21 January to John Scott Colley, Frank Grisham; 23 January to Allen Tate; 9 February to Robert A. McGaw; 10 February to Robert Penn Warren; 12 February to Allen Tate; 3 April to Allen Tate; 14 April to T. Daniel Young; F. 1-6. 17 April to Rob Roy Purdy; F.. 5-3. 21 April to O.B. Emerson; F. 1-6. 2 June to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 5-3. 10 June to Robert A. McGaw; F. 1-6. 24 June to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 5-3. 26.June to Allen Tate; 7 July to Helen Tate; F. 1-6. 9 July to Rob Roy Purdy; F. 5-3. 16 July to Robert A. McGaw; F. 1-6. 9 September to Gus G. Halliburton; F. 5-3. 15 September to Robert Penn Warren; 22 September to Robert A. McGaw; F. 1-6. 6 October to Rob Roy Purdy (2), T. Daniel Young; F. 5-3. 27 October to Rob Roy Purdy, Allen Tate; 5 November to T.D. Young; 17 November to Rob Roy Purdy; 16 December to Caroline Gordon; F. 1-6., 1975
- 6 January to Caroline Gordon; 13 January to John Hall Wheelock; 19 January to Lon (Brainard) Cheney; 12 February to Mrs. Buford Sanders; 16 February to Mrs. J.R. Hamblen; Mrs. Caroline Gordon Tate; 1 March to Rob Roy Purdy; 8 April to Allen Tate; 13 April to Robert A. McGaw; 3 May to Frank P. Grisham, Robert A. McGaw; 17 May to Sam M. Fleming, T. Daniel Young; 18.May to William Boozer; 1. June to Bob A. McGaw; 17 June to Robert A. McGaw; 26 July to Frank P. Grisham; 29'July to Frank P. Grisham; Allen Tate; 2 September to George Core; 10 September to Marilyn W. Whiteman, Allen Tate; 20 September to Rob Roy Purdy; 27 September to Robert A. McGaw; 18 October to Alexander Heard; 4 November to Frank P. Grisham; F. 1-6., 1976
- 10 January to Robert Penn Warren; F. 1-6., 1977
- Memorandum on Fugitive Room in the New Wing of the Joint University Library; F. 6-13. This is a name index of the correspondents of Jesse Ely Wills. The figure (or figures) in parentheses immediately following each name denotes the total number of letters from that person in the collection; the dates are for the time of the letters. The full name of the writer is given whenever possible. The last number given refers to the box and folder in which the correspondence may be found., n.d.
Index of Correspondents
Abeel, Ethel M.
Ansoff, H. Igor, (1); 10 November 1970; F. 6-11.
Basler, Roy P., (2); 20 June 1968; 4 December 1970; F. 6-13.
Batson, Randolph, (2); 11 May 1971; 30 November 1973; F. 1-6.
Batts, William 0., (1); 30 August 1956; F. 1-7.
Benson, Maxwell E., (1); 3 June 1959; F. 3-5.
Boswell, Dean (Mrs. John E.), (1) 5 May 1959; F. 3-5.
Boult, Reber, (2); 30 July 1965; F. 1-7.. 3 July 1968; F. 6-13.
Branscombe, Harvie, (11); 26 March 1957 (to William F. Orr); 23 January 1959 (to John Patterson); F. 6-19. 8 March 1960 (mimeographed statements and appendix I-III of 1 March through 3 March 1960); 30 May (Confidential to all Members of the Board of Trust); 13 June 1960 (A statement to the faculty of Vanderbilt University); 14 June 1960 (To all Members of the Board of Trust of Vanderbilt University); 10 January 1969 (to Alexander Heard); n.d. (To all Members of the Board of Trust); F. 6-14. 27 April 1970; 22 September 1973; F. 6-17.
Brooks, Cleanth, (1); 3 January 1976; F. 1-7.
Brown, Warren S., (1); 12 April 1972 (to Rob Roy Purdy); F. 6-7.
Buffington, Robert, (2); 3 April 1968; 3 April 1968 (to Mrs. Floy W.
Beatty); F. 1-7.
Campbell, Matthew M., (1); 20 October 1969; F. 6-10.
cassebeer. ~rcia (Mrs. F.W.), (1); 16 May 1959; F. 3-5.
Cheney, Brainard (Lon), (1); 1 January 1976; F. 1-7.
Cheney, Frances Nee! (Mrs. Brainard), (4); 17 June 1971 (to EllenWills), 22 November 1971, 4 February 1972 (to Centennial
Club's Literary Department); 17 October 1973; F. 1-7.
Cherry, Kenneth, (1); 6 May 1974; F. 1-7.
Cole, W.R., Jr., (1); 26 March 1960 (To each individual member of the
Board of Trust of Vanderbilt University); F. 6-14.
Coppolillo, Henry P., (1); 16 March 1972; F. 1-6.
Core, George, (1); 30 August 1976; F. 1-7.
Courtenay, Walter R., (1); 6 May 1959; F. 3-5.
Cowan, Louise S., (1); 12 July 1976; F. 1-7.
Crabb, A.L., (1); 23 April 1959; F. 3-5.
Crabtree, Lib (Mrs. R.D.), (2); 8 December 1958; F. 3-4.
11 April 1959; F. 3-5.
Crocker, David, (1); 4 January 1961 (to Billie, William F. Orr); F. 6-19.
Cuninggim, Merrbnon, (4); 16 July 1970 (to William Vaughn); 29 July 1970; F. 6-2. 29 March 1971; F. 6-8. 13 April 1973, 15 June 1976 (by Hattie R. Lane); F. 6-2.
Dameron, J. Lasley, (1); 16 February 1966 (to Vanderbilt University Press); F. 1-7.
Davidson, Donald, (8); 20 May 1954; 8 August 1962; F. 1-7. 28 March 1965; F. 4-5. 29 September 1966; 30 September 1966; 16 October 1966; 23 May 1967; 18 June 1967 (to Ellen Wills); F. 1-7.
DeWitt, John H., Jr., (7); 6 January 1964; 13 January 1964; n.d. (Memo about Westinghouse letter of 20 January 1964); 17 February 1964 (to James H. Quillen); 15 November 1965; 27 December 1965; 30 December 1965; F. 6-18.
Dickson, William, (1); 23 November 1969; F. 6-11.
Dockstader, Frederick J., (1); 16 December 1971; F. 1-7.
Duncan, Edgar H., (2); 16 February 1971; 22 December 1975; F. 1-7.
Dysart, Benjamin C., (1); 17 November 1969 (to Peter G. Hoadley); F. 6-10.
Earthman, B~rd Douglas, (1); 23 March 1970; F. 6-2.
Eight Doctoral Students Who Left the GSM Program, (1); 30 September 1975; F. 6-11.
Elliott, William Yandell, (6); 28 May 1958 (one addressed to Allen Tate); 20 February 1969 (to Allen Tate); 22 April 1969; 23 June 1969; 25 July 1969; 25 June 1970; F. 1-7.
Eutiekin, Mrs. Ervin, (1); 4 November 1969; F. 6-10.
Eyster, Rebecca, (1); 1 November 1966; F. 3-5.
Farrell, Louis, Jr., (1); 23 September 1969; F. 6-10.
Flack, James K., (1); 12 November 1967; F. 1-7.
Fleming, Sam M., (1); 15 May 1970 (to Rob Roy Purdy); F. 6-7.
Flowers, H. Fort, (4); 21 December 1965; Christmas 1965 (card); F. 6-12. 17 January 1969 (to Madison S. Wigginton); F. 6-5. 8 October 1969 (to Alexander Heard); F. 6-10.